$("#start").on("click", function() {
  $("#start").remove();
  console.log("you clicked start");
  for (var i = 0; i < questions.length; i++) {
    $("#questions").append("<h2>" + questions[i].question + "</h2>");
    for (var j = 0; j < questions[i].answers.length; j++) {
      $("#questions").append(
        "<input type='radio' name='question- " +
          i +
          "' value= '" +
          questions[i].answers[j] +
          "'>" +
          questions[i].answers[j]
      );
    }
  }
  game.start();
});

$(document).on("click", "#end", function() {
  game.done();
});

// function populate() {
//   if (quiz.isEnded()) {
//     showScores();
//   } else {
//     //show question
// var element = document.getElementById("question");
//     element.innerHTML = quiz.getQuestionsIndex().text;
//   }
// }

//questions
var questions = [
  {
    question: "In what season did the cube come?",
    answers: ["Season 4", "Season 5", "Season 6", "Season 7"],
    correctAnswer: "Season 5"
  },
  {
    question: "How many DJ skins have there been so far (up to Season 8)?",
    answers: ["One", "Two", "Four", "Five"],
    correctAnswer: "Two"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the weapon that got removed really fast?",
    answers: ["Sword", "Guided Missle", "Zapatron", "Burst AR"],
    correctAnswer: "Zapatron"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the dance that you get right when you first get the game?",
    answers: ["Dance Moves", "Orange Justice", "Hype", "Living Large"],
    correctAnswer: "Dance Moves"
  },
  {
    question: "How many types of ARs are there?",
    answers: ["Three", "Four", "Five", "Six"],
    correctAnswer: "Five"
  }
];

var game = {
  correct: 0,
  incorrect: 0,
  counter: 10,

  //timer count down from 10 seconds
  countdown: function() {
    game.counter--;
    $("#counter").html(game.counter);
    if (game.counter <= 0) {
      console.log("Time is up!");
      game.done();
    }
    if (game.counter === 0) {
      stop();
      alert("Time is Up!");
    }
    //   if (game.counter <= 0) {
    //       console.log("Time is up!");
    //       game.done();
    //   }
    //   if (game.counter === 0) {
    //       stop();
    //       alert("Time is Up!");
    //   }
  },
  start: function() {
    timer = setInterval(game.countdown, 1000);
    $("#card-timer").append(
      // $("#sub-wrapper#").prepend(
      '<h4><span id="counter">5</span> Seconds</h4>'
    );
    $("#start").remove();
    console.log("you clicked start");
    for (var i = 0; i < questions.length; i++) {
      $("#questions").append(questions[i].question);
      console.log(questions[i].question);
      //   $("#questions").append("<h3>" + questions[i].question + "</h3>");
      for (var j = 0; j < questions[i].answers.length; j++) {
        $("#questions").append(
          "<input type='radio' name='question- " +
            i +
            "' value= '" +
            questions[i].answers[j] +
            "'>" +
            questions[i].answers[j]
        );
      }
    }
    $("#sub-wrapper").append('<br><button id="end">DONE</button>');
  },
  done: function() {
    $.each($('input[name="question-1]":checked')),
      function() {
        if ($(this).val() == questions[1].correctAnswer) {
          game.correct++;
        } else {
          game.incorrect++;
        }
      };
    this.result();
  },
  result: function() {
    clearInterval(timer);
    $("#sub-wrapper h2").remove();

    $("#sub-wrapper").html("<h2>All done!</h2>");
    $("#sub-wrapper").append("<h3>Correct Answers: " + this.correct + "</h3>");
    $("#sub-wrapper").append(
      "<h3>Incorrect Answers: " + this.incorrect + "</h3>"
    );
    $("#sub-wrapper").append(
      "<h3>Unanswered: " +
        (questions.length + (this.incorrect + this.correct)) +
        "</h3>"
    );
  }
};

// var quiz = new Quiz(questions);

// populate();

// for (var i = 0; i < questions.length; i++) {
// var choices = window.text(questions[i].text);
// if(choices == questions[i].answer) {
//     score++;
//     alert("Correct!");
// }
// };

//try
//$ jquery instead of this function using this. "this" will work in function
//

// var number = 20;
// var intervalId;
// var score = 0;

// ]
// //when the Start button gets clicked run the start function
// $("#start").on(click, start);

// function start() {
//   clearInterval(intervalId);
//   intervalId = setInterval(decrement, 1000);
// }

// function decrement() {
//   number--;
//   $("#timer").html("<h2>" + number + "</h2>");
//   if (number === 0) {
//     stop();
//     alert("Time is Up!");
//   }
// }
// start();

// for(var i=0; i < questions.length; i++) {
// var response = window.prompt(questions[i].prompt);
// if(response == questions[i].answers) {
//     score++;
//     alert("Correct!");

// } else {
//     alert("That is incorrect.");
// }
// }
// alert("You got " + score + "/" + questions.length);

// //randomly select questions
// function getQuestions() {
//   return [
//     {
//       questionText: "Who sings Sunflower?",
//       options: ["Marshmellow", "Singer 2", "Singer 3", "Singer 4"],
//       correct: 0
//     },
//     {
//       questionText: "Question number 2?",
//       options: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
//       correct: 3
//     },
//     {
//       questionText: "Question number 3?",
//       options: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
//       correct: 2
//     },
//     {
//       questionText: "Question number 4?",
//       options: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
//       correct: 1
//     },
//     {
//       questionText: "Question number 5?",
//       options: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
//       correct: 3
//     },
//     {
//       questionText: "Question number 6?",
//       options: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
//       correct: 3
//     },
//     {
//       questionText: "Question number 7?",
//       options: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
//       correct: 3
//     },
//     {
//       questionText: "Question number 8?",
//       options: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
//       correct: 3
//     },
//     {
//       questionText: "Question number 9?",
//       options: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
//       correct: 3
//     },
//     {
//       questionText: "Question number 10?",
//       options: ["answer1", "answer2", "answer3", "answer4"],
//       correct: 3
//     }
//   ];
// }
// class Trivia extends React.Component {}
